{
    "id": "4f1076bb552d41e9b778a098b0107c97",
    "title": "Infinitives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Rahul …………… ……………… the letter yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "forgot, posting",
                "forgot, to post",
                "forgot, posted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3365a634737040e88db4fe1a92c8b97f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………… him why he ........................ angry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "asked, is",
                "asked, was",
                "ask, was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "80225eac81b4417a9a7865b0ad70e775"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor ………………. the patient …………………. his medicines without fail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised, to take",
                "advised, taking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b8122859648a44528925a693689bd5a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………..  for someone …………….. the lawn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "look, mow",
                "looking, to mow",
                "are looking, to mow",
                "are looking, mowing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "00b083f5890b4e9bbf86a38b6c571474"
        },
        {
            "question": "All the students ………………. …………………. in the program.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want, to participate",
                "want, participating",
                "want, participate"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1df2a41423ed46668b4fca938011f85b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………….. to the airport ……………… off my friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went, see",
                "went, to see",
                "went, seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3285f33ef8b1493dafdc24e633f6c3af"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bear ……………….. up the tree ………………. the honey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "climbing, to drink",
                "climbed, to drink",
                "climbed, drinking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6e52552177049689eaa7c14a71ad73d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last month we ……………… to Agra ……………. the Taj Mahal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went, seeing",
                "went, to see",
                "went, saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1b77b1a68e644f67a32c91274760f2d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ……………… the students ……………. hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "encouraging, working",
                "encouraged, working",
                "encouraged, to work"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43e01ecfae094db2a565792378056d5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. ………………. the first prize in the quiz competition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want, to win",
                "am wanting, to win",
                "want, winning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72a11346b2524f4c9a0fdddab2b075dd"
        }
    ]
}